# **Anamoul** Rouf

I'm a Product Designer with more than 7 years of working experience in building bridge between business, technology and human.

I believe in design practice that is data-informed and driven by empathy. I find the balance between complex business requirements and user needs, through a user-centric design approach.

## Work History

Product Design Manager at Truck Lagbe Limited From MAY 2021 to Continue.

Truck Lagbe is the largest and pioneer in truck & pickup rental service provider.

- I'm leading the most talented team of 5+ designers and design functional and useable products for the current 2M+ & future billion users.
- Conceive, plan and drive the development of high-end, useful digital products.
- · Facilitated the design team in developing and maintaining the design system, implementing the design process to increase team productivity by around 25%.

Sr. Product Designer at ShareTrip Inc. From SEP 2018 to APR 2021.

ShareTrip is the country's first and pioneer online travel aggregator (OTA).

- My goal was to craft a functional and delightful experience through web and mobile apps currently consisting of 1.2M+ & future billion users.
- Assembled informative insights from research and interviews. Made strategic decisions using rapidly testing and design thinking approach, improved usability by about 54%
- · Collaborated & co-ordinated with CEO, engineers, and other stakeholders to define UX problems and improve user engagement and generated about 56% growth in active users in 4 months.
- Designed and evaluated a centralized Design System. Maintained consistency and continuity, save around 25% of designers' and developers' productive time.
- · Created seamless and intuitive booking experience through the platform with about 86% success rate.

UX Consultant (part-time) at JoBike From JAN 2019 to From JUN 2019.

Jobike is an on-demand bicycle-sharing service. Worked on 3+ web & mobile apps.

- Redesign & automate the support system and also enhance the bicycle battery efficiency by 30%.
- Designed a more improved & secured user account recharge process, which helps to get positive user reviews.

UI & UX Designer at Beatnik Digital From FEB 2016 to FEB 2018

Beatnik is a 360 creative agency based in Dhaka, Bangladesh.

- Successfully worked on around 25+ web and mobile app design projects for many renowned brands like-Banglalink, Berger Paints BD, Burger King BD, Bengal Meet, IPDC Finance, etc.
- Convinced the importance of User Experience and engaged the core team and stakeholders throughout the design process. Led kick-off meetings, interviews, design studios, and user testings.

- **+880 175 969 3045**
- anamoulrouf.bd@gmail.com
- anamoulrouf.com
- anamoulrouf.com/portfolio
- in linkedin.com/in/roufuxdesigner

### Education

## Google UX

Google Career Certificates (Coursera) 2020 - 21

#### Design Thinking for Innovation

Darden School of Business (Coursera) 2020 - 21

#### Conducting Usability Testing

IDF 2020 - 21

# **Human-Centered Design**

UCSan Diego (Coursera) 2019 - 20

#### Gamification

University of Pennsylvania (Coursera) 2020 - 21

#### BBS, Business Studies

National University, Bangladesh 2005 - 09

#### + More

#### Skills

- User Interview
- Heuristic Evaluation
- Persona
- Competitor Analysis
  Usability Testing
- Scenario
- · Think Alouds
- Rapid Prototyping · Visual Design
- Storyboarding Contextual Inquiry
- · Design System
- Sketches
- Design
- Wireframing
- Documentation

#### + More

#### Tools

- Figma
- · Adobe XD
- FigJam Balsamia
- · Adobe Creative Suit
- Miro
- Zeplin Notion
- + More

# Work Interest

- Augmented Reality (AR) Virtual Reality (VR)
- · Design for Al-Driven Tech
- · User Survey Data Analysis.